<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Natificaton_Task</string>
    <string name="English">English</string>
    <string name="Arabic">Arabic</string>
    <string name="the_2022_fifa_world_cup_is_the_22nd_edition_of_the_men_s_national_team_world_cup_held_every_four_years_and_contested_by_the_member_national_teams_of_fifa_it_was_held_in_qatar_from_november_20_to_december_18_2022_making_it_the_first_world_cup_to_be_held_in_the_arab_world_and_the_islamic_world_and_the_second_edition_to_be_held_in_asia_after_the_2002_edition_in_south_korea_and_japan_france_were_the_defending_champions_having_defeated_croatia_4_2_in_the_2018_final_in_russia_at_an_estimated_cost_of_more_than_220_billion_this_edition_is_the_most_expensive_world_cup_held_so_far_this_figure_is_disputed_by_qatari_officials_including_the_organization_s_chief_executive_nasser_al_khater_who_said_the_real_cost_was_8_billion_and_other_figures_relating_to_overall_infrastructure_development_since_the_world_cup_was_awarded_to_qatar_in_2010_this_was_the_seventh_and_final_edition_with_32_teams_participating_starting_since_the_1998_world_cup_with_the_number_of_participating_teams_set_to_increase_to_48_in_the_2026_world_cup_to_avoid_the_dangers_of_qatar_s_hot_climate_the_tournament_was_held_during_the_months_of_november_and_december_making_it_the_first_the_tournament_is_not_held_during_the_summer_the_tournament_was_played_over_a_short_time_frame_of_29_days_with_64_matches_played_across_eight_venues_in_five_cities_the_qatari_national_team_automatically_qualified_as_the_host_team_along_with_31_teams_who_qualified_through_the_qualifiers_qatar_lost_all_three_of_its_matches_in_group_a_becoming_the_first_host_nation_to_lose_all_of_its_matches_making_it_the_second_host_team_to_be_eliminated_from_the_group_stage_after_2010_world_cup_host_south_africa_the_opening_match_of_the_tournament_was_held_on_november_20_2022_between_qatar_and_ecuador_at_the_ecuador_stadium_the_house_is_in_al_khor_and_the_final_match_was_held_on_december_18_2022_which_coincides_with_qatar_national_day">The 2022 FIFA World Cup is the 22nd edition of the men\'s national team World Cup, held every four years and contested by the member national teams of FIFA. It was held in Qatar from November 20 to December 18, 2022, making it the first World Cup to be held in the Arab world and the Islamic world and the second edition to be held in Asia after the 2002 edition in South Korea and Japan. France were the defending champions, having defeated Croatia 4–2 in the 2018 final in Russia. At an estimated cost of more than $220 billion, this edition is the most expensive World Cup held so far. This figure is disputed by Qatari officials, including the organization\'s chief executive Nasser Al Khater, who said the real cost was $8 billion, and other figures relating to overall infrastructure development since the World Cup was awarded to Qatar in 2010. This was the seventh and final edition with 32 teams participating (starting since the 1998 World Cup), with the number of participating teams set to increase to 48 in the 2026 World Cup. To avoid the dangers of Qatar\'s hot climate, the tournament was held during the months of November and December, making it the first The tournament is not held during the summer. The tournament was played over a short time frame of 29 days, with 64 matches played across eight venues in five cities. The Qatari national team automatically qualified as the host team, along with 31 teams who qualified through the qualifiers. Qatar lost all three of its matches in Group A, becoming the first host nation to lose all of its matches, making it the second host team to be eliminated from the group stage after 2010 World Cup host South Africa. The opening match of the tournament was held on November 20, 2022 between Qatar and Ecuador at the Ecuador Stadium. The house is in Al Khor, and the final match was held on December 18, 2022, which coincides with Qatar National Day.</string>
    <string name="feedback">feedback</string>
    <string name="Content_Title">Notificatons</string>
    <string name="rating">Rating</string>
    <string name="feedback_message">Feedback</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="feedback_dialog">Feedback</string>

</resources>